Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - RA Today, 2010 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, 2010 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, 2010 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, 2010 July 7; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 6)
  - Reports of Committees 1999-2000, 2000 July 3-6; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 8)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1999 Representative Assembly, 2000 July 3-6; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 9)
  - Representative Assembly A Today Pre-Annual Meeting, 2000; Series (Box 4879, Folder 4)
  - Representative Assembly Today, July 6, 2000; Series (Box 4879, Folder 5)
  - Regional Instructional Conference Booklets, 1951-1961; Series 1 (Box 4056, Folder 2)
  - [Regional Leadership Conference Miscellaneous Items], 2004; Series 1 (Box 4660, Folder 3)
  - Report on the 68th Annual Convention of the American Federation of Teachers, August 1984; series 1 (Box 4381, Folder 24)
  - Report of Staff Committee on Problems of Transition to the New Constitutional Convention Documents, January 19, 1972; Series 1 (Box 4056, Folder 3)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1988 Representative Assembly Presented to the 68th Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4971, Folder 9)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1990 Representative Assembly Presented to the 70th Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1991; Series 1 (Box 4971, Folder 10)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1992 Representative Assembly Presented to the 72th Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1993; Series 1 (Box 4971, Folder 11)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1993 Representative Assembly Presented to the 73rd Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4972, Folder 1)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1994 Representative Assembly Presented to the 74rd Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1995; Series 1 (Box 4972, Folder 2)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 2001 Representative Assembly Presented to the 81st Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 2002; Series 1 (Box 4972, Folder 2002)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1991 Representative Assembly Presented to the 71st Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 5-8; Series (Box 4832, Folder 1)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1993 Representative Assembly Presented to the 73rd Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 2)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1994 Representative Assembly Presented to the 74th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 3)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1996 Representative Assembly Presented to the 76th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 4)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1998 Representative Assembly Presented to the 77th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 5)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1999 Representative Assembly Presented to the 78th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 6)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1999 Representative Assembly Presented to the 79th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 7)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 2000 Representative Assembly Presented to the 80th Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 4-7; Series (Box 4832, Folder 8)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 2001 Representative Assembly Presented to the 81st Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 2-5; Series (Box 4832, Folder 9)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 2002 Representative Assembly Presented to the 82nd Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 3-6; Series (Box 4832, Folder 10)
  - Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 2003 Representative Assembly Presented to the 83rd Representative Assembly of the NEA, July 4-7; Series (Box 4832, Folder 11)
  - Reports of Committees 2002 - 2003: Presented to the 82nd Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, July 3-6; Series (Box 4831, Folder 12)
  - Reports of Committees, Councils, and Task Forces 1974-75 Presented to the Fifty-Fourth Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1975 July 2-8; Series 1 (Box 5051, Folder 11)
  - Reports of Committees Presented to the 56th Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1977 July 3-6; Series 1 (Box 5052, Folder 1)
  - Research Conference, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 7)
  - Research Conference (1991), 1990; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions Conference (1991), 1990; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions Meeting, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 1)
  - Retirement and Benefits Forum [file 1/3], 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 2)
  - Retirement and Benefits Forum [file 2/3], 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 3)
  - Retirement and Benefits Forum [file 3/3], 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Forum (1987), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Forum (1988, 1990) [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Forum (1988, 1990) [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1508, Folder 7)
  - The Right of America's Children, 2000 July 1-6; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 10)
  - The Right of America's Children, July 1-6; Series (Box 4879, Folder 12)
  - San Diego, circa 1990; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 1)
  - Salt Lake City Schools Western Music Educators Conference, 1959; Series 1 (Box 4933, Folder 3)
  - School Finance Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 2)
  - Site Selex, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 3)
  - Southeast Regional Leadership Conference (1989), 1988; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Plan and Budget Fiscal Years: 2000-2002, 2000 July; Series 1 (Box 4989, Folder 1)
  - Student NEA sign, signed by NEA President Jim Harris and all student delegates at the 1975 Representative Assembly, Series 1 (Box 5080, Folder 1)
  - Summary of the Conference on a National Policy for Educational Television Channel Assignments, 1964; series 1 (Box 4331, Folder 11)
  - Task Force and Committee Reports 1973-74 Presented to the Fifty-Third Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1974 June 28 - July 3; Series 1 (Box 5052, Folder 2)
  - Task Force and Other Reports Presented to the Fifty-Second Representative Assembly of the National Education Association, 1973 July 3-6; Series 1 (Box 5052, Folder 3)
  - Team NEA, Fighting for You, Your Schools, Your Students- 143rd Annual Meeting, July 1-6, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4706, Folder 2)
  - Toward Responsible Freedom, Undated; Series (Box 4869, Folder 5)
  - Uniserv Managers Meeting (1988), 1987; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 5)
  - Uniserv Managers [file 1/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 6)
  - Uniserv Managers [file 2/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 7)
  - Uniserv Training (1990), 1989; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 8)
  - United Legal Services Program (ULSP) Meeting (1991), 1989; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 9)
  - Washington Plaza Rejoining, circa 1989; Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 10)
  - Women's Leadership Program (1990), Series 1 (Box 1509, Folder 11)